tamilflame.com 2006-06-17

# Privacy Policy

At TamilFlame.Com, all personal information collected by us on this site (for example, on contests/sweepstakes entry forms) will be utilized primarily for internal purposes and/or to enhance visitor enjoyment and experience. We may also use email addresses or other personally identifiable information to contact visitors who directly communicate with, For example, to notify visitors that they have won a contest/sweepstakes or to provide a requested email newsletter. Visitors may voluntarily subscribe to newsletters. We provide visitors with an option to unsubscribe from future email newsletters. Sometimes, personal information submitted by visitors may be used for marketing and promotional purposes relating to the Web site or other entertainment properties. We don't share any personally identifiable information provided by visitors with third parties, unless specified at time of collection. We bear no responsibility for any action or policies of any third parties who collect any information visitors may disclose on the bulletin boards, chat areas or other public forums on this Web site. We request that all visitors to the Web site that are under the age of 18 not disclose or provide any personal information on this Web site unless they provide written authorization to us from their parent or legal guardian. We reserves the right to modify, alter or otherwise update this policy at any time so visitors are encouraged to review this policy from time to time.

We don't share any personally identifiable information provided by visitors with third parties, unless specified at time of collection. All information that is submitted on our site is stored securely and not shared with third parties. We take necessary and precautionary measures to secure our database.
